Quentin Levaslot - Web engineer

I'm fluent with back and frontend technologies, although I prefer the later. I understand every part of a project and if I don't know something I can find solutions quickly. I am used to work on small teams as technical lead, where i can share my expertise with others. My main focus nowadays is progressive web apps, applications making use of the latest web advances for the best user experience (offline web, push notifications, service worker caching...).

(+33) 6 52 74 17 37

quentin.levaslot@gmail.com http://github.com/QLevaslot French, 26 years old

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer at Capgemini

January 2014 - PRESENT

Currently tech lead on innovative management tools produced by Capgemini.

- \rightarrow Mix of devops and agile methodologies (scrum, spotify model, continuous delivery...)
- → React, Flux, Typescript, Spring boot.

Formerly tech lead on modern web applications for Leroy Merlin over a 2 years timeframe. Build and maintenance of several web based 2D product configurators (closets, bathrooms, custom rooms...). Build of a web based fidelity program.

→ AngularJS, canvas

Software Intern at Atos Worldline

July 2013 - December 2013

Development of a responsive web application. Administration interface of a delivery system to help the client track in real-time his workers and parcels. Java EE.

Software Intern at Nordsoft

June 2012 - August 2012

Contributing to the development of a collaborative web application aimed at creating and editing touristic guides. PHP with homemade framework.

EDUCATION

IT Master at UQAC

2012 - 2013

Double diploma. University of Quebec at Chicoutimi, Canada.

Engineering school at HEI

2008 - 2013

Engineering student at HEI (High Engineering Studies), France. All-around engineering school, IT specialization. Master equivalency.

SKILLS

Frontend

ReactJS, Flux, Redux, Node.js, ES6/7, AngularJS, Gulp, SASS

Backend

Node, Spring, Java

Management

Agile methodologies (Scrum, spotify model...), Devops

LANGUAGES

French - native

English – full professional proficiency

INTERESTS

Guitar, rugby, biking